export const economics = [
    {
        choices: ["Material update", "Material count", "Physical inventory", "Technological assessment"],
        correctAnswer: "Physical inventory",
        question: "Consists of the actual counting or determination of the actual quantity of the materials on hand as of a given date.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Recreation center", "Business", "Buy and sell section", "Market"],
        correctAnswer: "Market",
        question: "The place where buyers and sellers come together. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["inflation", "depletion", "incremental cost", "Depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "depletion",
        question: "The lessening of the value of an asset due to the decrease in the quantity available (referring to tha natural resources, coal, oil, etc.)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Goods", "Supply", "Demand", "Stocks"],
        correctAnswer: "Supply",
        question: "The quantity of a given commodity that is offered for sale at a certain price at a given place and time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["nominal rate", "exact interest rate", "rate of return", "effective rate"],
        correctAnswer: "effective rate",
        question: "We may classify an interest rate, which specifies the actual rate of interest on the principal for one year as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["loss", "capital expenditure", "deficit", "capital loss"],
        correctAnswer: "capital loss",
        question: "The reduction in the money value of a capital asset is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Goodwill value", "Fair value", "Going value", "Book value"],
        correctAnswer: "Going value",
        question: "An intangible value which is actually operating concern has due to its operation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Capital gain", "Time deposit", "Bond", "Certificate of deposit"],
        correctAnswer: "Certificate of deposit",
        question: "It is a negotiable claim issued by the bank in lieu of a term deposit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["the partners are not liable for the liabilities of the partnership.", "the partners personal assets are attached to the debt of the partnership", "the partnership assets(excluding the partners personal assets) only will be used to pay the liabilities.", "the partners may sell stock to general additional capital"],
        correctAnswer: "the partners personal assets are attached to the debt of the partnership",
        question: "In case of bankruptcy of a partnership,",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["tort", "negligence", "material breach", "fraud"],
        correctAnswer: "tort",
        question: "An evil wrong committed by a person damaged another person&amp;amp;#39;s property or reputation is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["interest rate", "investment", "all of the above", "interest"],
        correctAnswer: "interest rate",
        question: "The ratio of the interest payment to be principal for a given unit of time and usually expressed as a percentage of the principal. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Chairman of the Board", "Board of Directors", "Stockholders", "President"],
        correctAnswer: "Chairman of the Board",
        question: "What is the highest position in the corporation? ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["dC/dP = 0", "dC/dP = 1", "dC/dP = +1", "dC/dP = CO"],
        correctAnswer: "dC/dP = 0",
        question: "An economic study is made of the total amount cost (C) for a series of alternative investment (P) for a given project. If C is plotted as the ordinate versus P, the most desirable occurs when",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Treasury bill", "Money market", "Certifcate of deposit", "Hard currency"],
        correctAnswer: "Hard currency",
        question: "A currency traded in a foreign exchange market for which the demand is consistently high in relation to its supply",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Straight line method", "Sinking fund method", "SYD method", "Declining balance method"],
        correctAnswer: "Declining balance method",
        question: "Which of the following depreciation methods cannot have a salvage value of zero?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Simple annuity", "Progressive annuity", "Delayed annuity", "Deffered annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "Deffered annuity",
        question: "It is a series of equal payments occuring at equal intervals of time where the first payment is made after several periods, after the beginning of the payment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Demand factor", "Present worth factor", "Capacity factor", "Sinking fund factor"],
        correctAnswer: "Sinking fund factor",
        question: "The function of interest rate and time taht determines the cumulative amount of a sinking fund resulting from specific periodic deposits.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["bond", "check", "coupon", "bank notes"],
        correctAnswer: "coupon",
        question: "A document that shows proof of legal ownership of a financial security.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["salvage value", "book value", "future value", "replacement value"],
        correctAnswer: "salvage value",
        question: "Scrap value of an asset is sometimes know as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Oligopoly", "Bilateral Oligopsony", "Oligopsony", "Bilaterial Oligopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "Bilaterial Oligopoly",
        question: "A market situation where there are few sellers and few buyers.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Corporation", "Sole proprietorship", "Enterprise", "Partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "Sole proprietorship",
        question: "Is the simples form a business organization.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Oligopoly", "Monopoly", "Monopsony", "Oligopsony"],
        correctAnswer: "Monopoly",
        question: "A market situation where there is only one seller with many buyer.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["1000", "50", "100", "500"],
        correctAnswer: "500",
        question: "The letter D in the Roman numerals is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["how many years money will double", "how many years money will triple", "how many years to a mass 1 million", "how many years to quadruple the money"],
        correctAnswer: "how many years money will double",
        question: "The 72 rule of thumb is used to determine",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Preferred stock", "Bond", "Common stock", "T-bill"],
        correctAnswer: "Bond",
        question: "A certifcate of indebtness of a corporation usually for a period not less than 10 years and guaranteed by a mortgage on certain assets of the corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Monopoly", "Perfect competition", "Oligopoly", "Elastic demand"],
        correctAnswer: "Perfect competition",
        question: "This occurs in a situtation where a commodity or service is supplied by a number of vendors entering the market.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["T-bills", "All of these", "Bond", "Certificate of deposit"],
        correctAnswer: "Bond",
        question: "A form of fixed-interest security issued by central or local government, companies, banks or other institutions. They are usually a form of long-term security, buy may be irredeemable, secured or unsecured. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Escalatory clause", "Contigency clause", "Secondary clause", "Main clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Escalatory clause",
        question: "The provision in the contract that indicates the possible adjustment of material cost and labor cost.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["an owner&amp;amp;#39;s equity", "an expenses", "an asset", "a liability"],
        correctAnswer: "an asset",
        question: "Work-in process is classified as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Market value", "Goodwill value", "Book value", "Franschise value"],
        correctAnswer: "Franschise value",
        question: "The intangible item of value from the exclusive right of a company in a stated region of the country.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deflation", "devaluation", "depreciation", "inflation"],
        correctAnswer: "deflation",
        question: "Reduction in the level of national incom and output usually accompanied by the fall in the general price level.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Subscribed capital", "Money market", "Authorized capital", "Investment"],
        correctAnswer: "Authorized capital",
        question: "Grand total of the assets and operational capability of a corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Utility", "Supply", "Market", "Demand"],
        correctAnswer: "Demand",
        question: "The quantity of a certain commodity that is brought at a certain price at a given time and place.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["All of these", "Intangible assets", "Fixed assets", "Trade investments"],
        correctAnswer: "All of these",
        question: "Everything a company owns and which has a money value is classified as an asset. Which of the following is classified as an asset ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["first cost + salvage value", "annual costf", "first cost + interest of perpetual maintenance", "irst cost + interest of the first cost"],
        correctAnswer: "first cost + interest of perpetual maintenance",
        question: "Capitalized cost of any property is equal to the ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Monopsony", "Bilateral monopsony", "Bilateral monopoly", "Monopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "Bilateral monopoly",
        question: "A market situation where there is one seller and one buyer.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Registered bond", "Joint bond", "Mortgage bond", "Coupon bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Mortgage bond",
        question: "If the security of the bond is a mortgage on certain specified asset of a corporation, this bond is calssified as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["O and M costs", "Operating and maintenance costs", "GS and A expense", "Prime cost"],
        correctAnswer: "Prime cost",
        question: "DIrect labor cost incurred in the factory and direct materials cost are the costs of all materials that go into production. The sum of these two direct costs is known as.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["book value", "capital recovery", "sinking fund", "depreciation recovery"],
        correctAnswer: "depreciation recovery",
        question: "THe present worth of all depreciation over the economic life of the item is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["logarithms", "integrationd", "derivatives", "implicit functions"],
        correctAnswer: "logarithms",
        question: "To triple the principal, one must use",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Sinking fund method", "SYD method", "Declining balance method", "Straight line method"],
        correctAnswer: "Sinking fund method",
        question: "A method of depreciation where a fixed sum of money is regularly deposited at compound interest in a real or imaginary fund in order to accumulate an amount equal to the total depreciation of an asset at the end of the asset&amp;amp;#39;s estimated life.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Collateral trust bond", "Mortgage", "Registered bond", "Coupon bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Collateral trust bond",
        question: "A type of bind where the corporation pledges securities which it owns (i,e, stocks, bonds of its subsidiaries)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Depletion", "Depreciation", "Book value", "Scrap value"],
        correctAnswer: "Depreciation",
        question: "The reduction of the value of an asset due to constant use and passage of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Its life is dependent on the lives of the incorporators.", "it is the not best form of business organization.", "The stockholders of the corporation are only liable to the extent of their investments.", "The minimum number of incorporators to start a corporation is three."],
        correctAnswer: "The stockholders of the corporation are only liable to the extent of their investments.",
        question: "Which is true about corporation?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Demented persons", "Dead persons", "Minors", "Senior citizens"],
        correctAnswer: "Demented persons",
        question: "Parties whose consent or signature in a contract is not considered intelligent.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Corporation", "Company", "Sole proprietorship", "Partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "Partnership",
        question: "An association of two or more individuals for the purpose of operating a business as co-workers for profit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Straight line method", "SYD method", "Declining balance method", "Sinking fund method"],
        correctAnswer: "Declining balance method",
        question: "A method of computing depreciation in which the annual charge is a fixed percentage of the depreciation book value at the beginning of the year to which the depreciation applies.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["n(n+1)/2", "n(n-1)", "n(n-1)/2", "n(n+1)"],
        correctAnswer: "n(n+1)/2",
        question: "In SYD method, the sum of years digit is calculated using the formula with n = number of useful years of the equipment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Discount", "Luxury", "Necessity", "Utility"],
        correctAnswer: "Luxury",
        question: "It is defined to be the capacity of a commodity to satisfy human want.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["General Agreement of Tariff and Trade", "Global Agreement of Tariff and Trade", "General Arrangement of Tariff and Trade", "Global Arrangement of Tariff and Trade"],
        correctAnswer: "General Agreement of Tariff and Trade",
        question: "GATT stands for",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["cash flow", "capital recovery", "economic return", "earning value"],
        correctAnswer: "cash flow",
        question: "The flow back of profit plus depreciation from a given project is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sinking fund", "demand factor", "present worth factor", "load factor"],
        correctAnswer: "present worth factor",
        question: "A mathematical expression also known as the present value of a n annuity of one called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Monopoly", "Oligopoly", "Oligopsony", "Monopsony"],
        correctAnswer: "Monopsony",
        question: "A market whereby there is only one buyer of an item for which there are no good substitute.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["gross margin", "profit margin", "rate of return", "net income"],
        correctAnswer: "gross margin",
        question: "Gross profit, sales less cost of good sold, as a percentage of a sales is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["capital expenditure", "profit", "capital stock", "capital gain"],
        correctAnswer: "capital gain",
        question: "An increase in the value of a capital assets is called ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["currency devaluation", "currency float", "currency depreciation", "currency appreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "currency devaluation",
        question: "The deliberate lowering of the price of a nation&amp;amp;#39;s currency in terms of the accepted standard (Gold, American dollar or the British pound)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Depletion", "Inflation", "Depreciation", "Recession"],
        correctAnswer: "Depreciation",
        question: "Decrease in the value of a physical property due to the passage of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["stock", "utility", "necessity", "commodity"],
        correctAnswer: "commodity",
        question: "Any particular raw material or pirmary product (e.g. cloth, wool, flour, coffee..) is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Registered bond", "Colalteral trust bond", "Debenture bond", "Joint bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Joint bond",
        question: "A type of bond issued jointly by two or more corporations.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Fair value", "Book value", "Salvage value", "Market value"],
        correctAnswer: "Salvage value",
        question: "Estimated value at the end of the useful life. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Monopoly", "Perfect competition", "Oligopoly", "Semi-monopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "Oligopoly",
        question: "A condition where only few individuals produce a certain product and that any action of one will lead to almost the same action of the others.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["principal", "maturity value", "loan", "interest"],
        correctAnswer: "interest",
        question: "The payment for the use of borrowed money is called ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["It will be dissolved if one of the partners ceases to be connected with the partnership", "It can be handed down from one generation of partners to another.", "Its capitalization must be equal for each partner.", "It has a perpetual life."],
        correctAnswer: "It will be dissolved if one of the partners ceases to be connected with the partnership",
        question: "Which is TRUE about partnership?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Book value", "Market value", "Face value", "Scrap value"],
        correctAnswer: "Book value",
        question: "The worth of the property equals to the original cost less depreciation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Common stick", "Incorporator&amp;amp;#39;s stock", "Preferred stock", "Authorization capital stock"],
        correctAnswer: "Preferred stock",
        question: "Represents the ownership, and enjoys certain preferences than ordinary stock.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["intangible assets", "current assets", "fixed assets", "trade invesments"],
        correctAnswer: "fixed assets",
        question: "Land, buildings, plant and machinery are examples of ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Ordinary annuity", "Perpetuity", "Deffered annuity", "Annuity due"],
        correctAnswer: "Ordinary annuity",
        question: "A type of annuity where the payments are made at the end of each payment period starting from the first period.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Capital recovery", "Annuity", "Annuity factor", "Amortization"],
        correctAnswer: "Amortization",
        question: "As applied to a capitalized asset, the distribution of the initial cost by a periodic changes to operation as in depreciation of the reduction of a debt by either periodic or irregular prearranged program is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Registered bond", "Debenture bond", "Infrastructure bond", "Equipments obligations bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Equipments obligations bond",
        question: "A type of bond whose guaranty is in lien on railroad equipments.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Return", "Par value", "Dividend", "Share stock"],
        correctAnswer: "Dividend",
        question: "The amount of company&amp;amp;#39;s profit that the board of directors of the corporation decides to distribute to ordinary shareholders. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Discount", "Interest", "Profit", "Credit"],
        correctAnswer: "Interest",
        question: "Money paid for the use of borrowed capital.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["10", "5", "3", "7"],
        correctAnswer: "5",
        question: "What is the minimum number of incorporators in order that a corporation be organized?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Depreciation", "Bond", "Sinking fun", "Amnesty"],
        correctAnswer: "Depreciation",
        question: "An artificial expenses that spreads the purchase price of an asset or another property over a number of years.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Shopping center", "Department store", "Mall", "Market"],
        correctAnswer: "Market",
        question: "The place where sellers and buyers come together. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Utility", "Luxuries", "Necessity", "Discount"],
        correctAnswer: "Luxuries",
        question: "Defined as the capacity of commodity to satisfy human want.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Partnership", "Enterprise", "Corporation", "Sole of proprietor"],
        correctAnswer: "Enterprise",
        question: "Which is NOT a type of business organization? ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Sole partnership", "Enterprise", "Partner", "Corporation"],
        correctAnswer: "Corporation",
        question: "Double taxation is a disadvantage of which business organization?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Incorporators stock", "Preferred stock", "Authorized capital stock", "Common stock"],
        correctAnswer: "Common stock",
        question: "Represents the ownership of stockholders who have residual claim on the assets of the corporation after all other claims have been settled.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Enterprise", "Corporation", "Sole proprietorship", "Partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "Partnership",
        question: "An association of two or more persons for a purpose of engaging in a profitable business",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["installation expenses", "initial taxes and permits fee", "all of the above", "The original purchase price and freight and transportation charges"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above",
        question: "The first cost of any property includes",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Compound interest is paid on all amounts in annuity.", "The first payment is made at the beginning of each period.", "The amounts of all payments are equal.", "The payments are made at equal interval of time."],
        correctAnswer: "The first payment is made at the beginning of each period.",
        question: "Which is NOT an essential element of an ordinary annuity?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Perpetuity", "Deffered annuity", "Annuity due", "Ordinary annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "Deffered annuity",
        question: "It is a series of equal payments occuring at equal interval of time where the first payment is made after several periods, after the beginning of the payment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Book value", "Salvage value", "Scrap value", "Going value"],
        correctAnswer: "Salvage value",
        question: "Sometimes called second hand value.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Private", "Pure", "Analytic", "Gratuitous"],
        correctAnswer: "Gratuitous",
        question: "Kind of obligation which has no condition attached. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Per value", "Equity", "Dividend", "Return"],
        correctAnswer: "Equity",
        question: "The residual value of a company&amp;amp;#39;s assets after all outside liabilities (shareholders excluded) has been allowed for.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["acid-test ratio", "current ratio", "profit margin ratio", "receivable turn-over"],
        correctAnswer: "acid-test ratio",
        question: "An index of short term paying ability is called ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Time value of money", "Present worth factor", "Interest rate", "Yield"],
        correctAnswer: "Time value of money",
        question: "The cumulative effect of elapsed time on the money value of an event, based on the earning power of equivalent invested funds capital should or will learn.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["present worth", "salvage value", "scrap value", "book value"],
        correctAnswer: "book value",
        question: "The recorded current value of an asset is known as ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Effective rate", "Nominal rate", "Rate of return", "Yield"],
        correctAnswer: "Rate of return",
        question: "The interest rate at which the present work of the cash on a project is zero of the interest earned by an investment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["All of these", "Incorporators bond", "Registered bond", "Preferred bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Registered bond",
        question: "A type of bond where the corporation&amp;amp;#39;s owners name are recorded and the interest is paid periodically to the owners with their asking for it.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Utilities", "Necessities", "Products goods and services", "Luxuries"],
        correctAnswer: "Necessities",
        question: "These are products or services that are required to support human life and activities, that will be purchased in somewhat the same quantity even though the price varies considerably.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Product goods and services", "Necessities", "Utilities", "Luxuries"],
        correctAnswer: "Luxuries",
        question: "These are products or services that are desired by humans and will be purchased if money is available after the required necssities have been obtained.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["none of the above", "total assets", "fixed assets", "current assets"],
        correctAnswer: "current assets",
        question: "Liquid assets such as cash and other assets that can be converted quickly into cash, such as accounts receivable and merchandise are called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Coupon bond", "Collateral trust bond", "Mortgage bond", "Registered bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Coupon bond",
        question: "Bond to which are attached coupons indicating the interest due and the date when such interest is to be paid.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["expected return", "interest", "nominal interest", "effective interest"],
        correctAnswer: "effective interest",
        question: "The true value of interest rate computed by equations for compound interest for a 1 year period is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Private", "Pure", "Equitable", "Public"],
        correctAnswer: "Private",
        question: "Type of the ownership in business where individuals exercise and enjoy the right in their own interest.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["In-place value", "Balanced sheet", "Break even-no gain loss", "Check and balance"],
        correctAnswer: "Check and balance",
        question: "The total income equals the total operating cost. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Enterprise", "Sole of proprietorship", "Partnership", "Corporation"],
        correctAnswer: "Corporation",
        question: "A distinct legal entity which can practically transact any business transaction which a real person could do.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Fair value", "Book value", "Slavage value", "Market value"],
        correctAnswer: "Book value",
        question: "Worth of the property as shown in the accounting records of an enterprise.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Physical life", "Economic life", "All of the above", "Operating life"],
        correctAnswer: "Economic life",
        question: "The length of time which the property may be operated at a profit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Law of diminishing return", "Law of demand", "Law of supply", "Law of supply and demand"],
        correctAnswer: "Law of supply and demand",
        question: "&amp;amp;quot;When free competition exists, the price of a product will be that value where supply is equal to the demand.&amp;amp;quot; ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Economic return", "Yield", "Expected yield", "Earning value"],
        correctAnswer: "Economic return",
        question: "The profit derived from a project or business enterprise without consideration of obligations to financial contributions or claims of other based on profit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Consumer saving", "Compulsory saving", "All of these", "Forced saving"],
        correctAnswer: "Forced saving",
        question: "A saving which takes place because goods are not available for consumption rather than the consumer really want to save. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["interest, taxes, rent, power cost, oil cost", "Amortization, insurance, steam cost, painting, cleaning", "interest, taxes, replcements, labor for repairs", "Interest, taxes, amortization, insurance, rent"],
        correctAnswer: "Interest, taxes, amortization, insurance, rent",
        question: "Which one of the following contains only items which are considered fixed charges?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Perpetuity", "Annuity", "Depreciation", "Inflation"],
        correctAnswer: "Perpetuity",
        question: "A series of uniform accounts over an infinite period of times",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Salvage value", "Fair value", "Book value", "Market value"],
        correctAnswer: "Market value",
        question: "It is the amount which a willing buyer will pay to a willing seller for a property where each has equal advantage and is under no compulsion to buy or sell. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Law of diminishing return", "Law of supply", "Law of demand and supply", "Law of demand"],
        correctAnswer: "Law of diminishing return",
        question: "&amp;amp;quot;When one of the factors or production is fixed in quantity or is difficult to increase, increasing the other factors of production will result in a less than proportionate increase in output&amp;amp;quot;.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["duopoly", "oligopsony", "duopsony", "oligopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "duopsony",
        question: "A market situation where there are only two buyers with many sellers.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Aiⁿ", "Ai", "A/i", "Aⁿ/i"],
        correctAnswer: "A/i",
        question: "A is a periodic payment and I is the interest rate, then present worth of a Perpetuity =",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Capital gain", "Internal rate of return", "Debenture", "Goodwill"],
        correctAnswer: "Capital gain",
        question: "It is the profit obtained by selling stocks at a higher price than its original purchase price",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Demand", "Utility", "Supply", "Market"],
        correctAnswer: "Supply",
        question: "The quantity of a certain commodity that is offered for sale at a certain price at a given time and place.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Fair value", "Goodwill value", "Market value", "Franchise value"],
        correctAnswer: "Fair value",
        question: "The value which has a disinterested third party, different from the buyer and seller, will determine in order to establish a price acceptable to both parties.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Current accounts", "Working capital", "Initial investment", "Subscribed capital"],
        correctAnswer: "Working capital",
        question: "Those funds that are required to make the enterprise or project a going concern.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["currency appreciation", "currency devaluation", "currency float", "currency depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "currency depreciation",
        question: "It denotes the fall in the exchange rate of one currency in terms of others. The term usually applies to floating exchange rates.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Debenture bond", "Registered bond", "Collateral trust bond", "Mortgage bond"],
        correctAnswer: "Debenture bond",
        question: "A type of bond which does not have security except a promise to pay by the issuing corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Annuity due", "Deffered annuity", "Perpetuity", "Ordinary annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "Annuity due",
        question: "A type of annuity where the payments are made at the start of each period, beginning from the first period.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Cash", "Patents", "Furniture", "Investment in subsidiary companies"],
        correctAnswer: "Patents",
        question: "Which an example of an intangible asset?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Declining balance method", "Striaght line method", "SYD method", "SInking fund method"],
        correctAnswer: "Declining balance method",
        question: "A method of depreciation whereby the amount to recover is spread uniformly over the estimated life of the asset in terms of the periods or units of output.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["discount (1)", "capital", "discount (2)", "interest"],
        correctAnswer: "discount (2)",
        question: "Defined as the future value minus the present value. ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Delict", "Technological assessment", "Bid bulletin", "Escalatory"],
        correctAnswer: "Bid bulletin",
        question: "Additional information of prospective bidders on contract documents issued prior to bidding date",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Annuity", "Deposit", "Debt", "Amortization"],
        correctAnswer: "Annuity",
        question: "It is a series of equal payments occuring at equal interval of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["6 years", "4 years", "7 years", "5 years"],
        correctAnswer: "6 years",
        question: "An amount of money invested at 12% interest per annum will double in approximately",
        topic: "NA"
    },
]